Welcome to submit subtitles to us via Email:
kisskh.me@gmail.com
I succeeded.
The Buddha Master
We 've been walking for so long that we haven't found forty-one.
Will they not even come in
Now if Wuye's dog is there
That's good.
Even with a dog.
I will only listen to the Fifth Master.
Then I'll adopt one as a child.
Don't you just
After this is over.
I also asked him for one.
Then you can change your name
Change what name
Dog 8
Eight dogs.
It's quite prestige
Good thing I just want a dog
The Buddha Master
Be careful.
Keep up
Yes
Little fish
You see if it's 40-1
Who are you?
Name
Buddha is a dummy
Hunting trap
The Buddha Master
These don't look like things from the next building.
It looks quite new.
Buddha, come and see
That’s strange.
Why are there lights here?
Buddha has words on it
Far East Reclamation Medal
It's Japanese
A sign of voluntary labor clearing.
Down here.
Why are there Japanese?
Bandage his wounds
We keep going in
The Japanese are involved here.
It's not simple
The Buddha Master
This is a Japanese fortification.
It seems that there are a lot of Japanese here.
It's a cross-fire blockade.
In this building.
There's something they're very afraid
Is that the Shadow?
It’s not that simple.
How could the Japanese possibly know about this Otherworld Pavilion?
What have they come here to do?
If the Japanese had anything to do with this
It must be a huge conspiracy
The building is only a small part.
They must have done a lot more as well.
The things we don’t know
We can't delay any longer
The game is already a lost cause.
Why bother wasting your energy again?
Changes in the Bureau
The Difference of the Only Son
Old Jiu, old Jiu
Still so stubborn
But this time
No matter how you calculate
Even if I can't keep myself
Information on your status as a student studying in Japan
Military Ministry delivered today
This period
I'm afraid there are not less than 10,000 people studying in Japan.
Chief Huo thinks they're all day long.
Those students are not like you.
They don't know as well as you and Mushu.
I only have personal friendship with Kumoto.
Just personal
The somebody else is open
Head of the Japan General Chamber of Commerce
You used just one letter three years ago
Let people withdraw all their funds.
The Japanese investment in the Crescent Hotel
Completely fall short
Under the wood is my classmate friend
During My study abroad, my tutor was biased against me.
It's Kookhunder to help me
I just graduated smoothly
I owe him a favor
Something in the letter
I just reported the kindness at that time.
Repend kindness
So you admit
You and the Japanese General Chamber of Commerce have already colluded.
No wonder your goods for so many years
Can be sold to Japan
Business can do so well.
If you have evidence
You can arrest me.
Old Nine ah
I'm from the Huo family
He is also a nine-door man.
If not as a last resort
I really don't want to move your
Sign it.
Hand over the money earned through daily operations to the government.
I’ll keep you safe.
By your ability
In a few years, a new name will be able to make a comeback.
The surname Jie has been passed down from our ancestors.
Must never be lost
I didn’t expect that.
Ninth Master is willing to die for a name
Also don't know is smart
Still stupid
Japanese Ministry of Internal Affairs
Another spy tried to get into Changsha and was killed.
The Japanese are really interested in Changsha
In order to avoid suspicion
You just stay here
Plaster flag
The Buddha Master
It's Japanese soldiers
It's all a self-cutting
It's all suicide.
The Buddha Master
That’s so strange.
These Japanese soldiers are obviously studying this building.
How good
They all committed suicide by mass abdominal cutting
So much living material.
It is no problem to live
If they're stuck too long
It has been confirmed that it cannot be done again.
It is also possible to commit suicide in despair.
Heart born of despair
It's impossible to live so orderly
Moreover
So many people
Despair together and cut the abdomen together
This is too puzzling
I feel very familiar with the system here.
Carefully search every corner
I think there will be some Harvest
Buddha, look
Meizhi Hatoyama
Who is Meizhi Hatoyama
You weren't there
Not knowing is normal.
Is an old acquaintance
No wonder Buddha thinks the system here looks familiar.
Meizhi Hatoyama is a Japanese adventurer
Japanese spy sneaks into Changsha to look for meteorite copper
Do you know this?
Listen to Buddha said
Hatoyama Meizhi is very cautious
Then why didn't he burn all the files
So many supplies here
None of the information was destroyed.
Unreasonable
So I say these people
Not necessarily suicide.
Evil Death Insanity
It's possible not to destroy the data, right?
The Buddha must have analyzed it long ago.
It's not like you have to be stubborn with me.
And this share
Say No.
That's it. That's it. That's it.
The Buddha Master
This is Japanese
He smells fish.
When will he be Japanese
Over the past few years, the Japanese have moved more and more.
The Buddha sent him to learn Japanese.
In order to be prepared early
Prepare for a rainy day
The Buddha Master
This is a supplement to the Hatoyama Report.
This is Hatoyama's submission to the Ministry of Foreign Affairs.
The Hatoyama Report, full volume
Revise a draft
More than thirty years ago
Japanese Kori Daigi
On the grounds of exploration in Central Asia
Bring in a large number of Footman students
Deep into the hinterland of China
Five years ago
When passing through Changsha
Branch of his expedition team
By Japanese merchant explorer
Mizhi Hatoyama Led
In the north of Changsha city
One hundred and sixty kilometers away in a mountain town
Stay for nearly three months
One week later
Yukiyama Michi
Transfer to the Ministry of Foreign Affairs of Japan's Nippon-Qing Trade Research Institute
Submitted a sixteen-page report
The Hatoyama Report
In his report he mentioned
Under the mountain town of Changsha
Buried something.
That is, the meteorite copper that Buddha later found.
Everybody thought
After the meteorite copper was found, the matter was over.
But in fact
The Hatoyama Report has a supplementary document
The level of confidentiality of this supplementary document
Even more than the original Hatoyama Report
Even higher
Mentioned in the document
Another place underground in Changsha
There seems to be a copper than a meteorite
More important things
Hatoyama Meizhi finally suggested giving up meteorite copper
Go all out to find this
Boss
How to sell this jade fish
Which one do you fancy
Let me introduce you
All those who should come in have come in
Let's go and meet our people.
It seems that the world building is for the Japanese.
More important than copper.
Of those who cut themselves
Do you have Hatoyama Meizhi
Judging by the way they're dressed
They're all soldiers.
Hatoyama should not be here
Buddha, look
This is a photo of them before they entered the country.
This is not only the number of people
And at least half of them aren't here
The Buddha Master
To say so
Meizhi Hatoyama must be in this building
In a deeper place
The Buddha Master
Found some more journals
So much information has not been destroyed.
There is another possibility.
Is that they think that entering this building
There's no chance of getting out alive.
Fifth Master
It's great that you're okay
We're all worried sick
Fifth Master
What’s wrong, Fifth Master?
Roller blind
Where are you hurt?
I didn’t do that.
Are you really okay?
It's okay.
Do you remember
What just happened
Remember
We have received
The painting you asked Bald to pass on.
I did it again according to what the letter said.
Result
I came here all at once.
What's the matter, Fifth Master?
Five Master Five Master
Fifth Master
Black Wind
Ao Lie
Fifth Master, where have you been
We were terribly worried.
Fifth Master, I knew you would be fine.
Fifth Brother
Seventh Sister
Did something just happen
After going back
Let’s get married.
What
Listen to me.
Now the Huo family sees you as a thorn in their side.
Ding Qiansi is even more difficult for you.
Although you are in a high position in the Hogan family
But it must have been very hard
Come to the Wu family
The same can be in charge
The same is among the nine doors
Nothing will change
But I will protect you
Don't let you suffer any injustice
Seventh Sister
Did something happen to you just now?
I think I just had a dream.
I dreamed of my past life.
He is the owner of an embroidery workshop.
In the dream
Have a little sister
Have an aunt
It must be this building.
Tell me in detail
Now all this is happening
We haven't figured out why
Right now
Let's get down to business first.
Okay?
None of the Fifth Master Zhang's family came.
Do you need to whistle to give them a signal?
Don't wait for them
Save the canopy and the three-inch nail first.
Fifth Master
We're trapped
Fifth Master is really Tianpeng. They
Beware of the mechanism.
Search separately
This is Yin and Yang buckle
Yang buckle here
Yin buckle in other places
Both sides need to be operated at the same time to unlock
This time
Absolutely must not be missed
I'll go find Yin Knot
You only leave two people
Remember
The formula for cracking the organ is three on the left and two on the right.
Left one right three
Left four left two
A little while later
No matter what you hear
Must be in accordance
I now tell you the formula to come
Especially the last step.
It's two squares to the left.
Never go wrong
Yes
Fifth Brother
There's something you're not telling us
That's right
But it's not a big deal
You believe me
Let's get out alive first.
I'll check with you slowly after I go out.
Will it work?
Rolling shutter old Seven is responsible for cracking the organ
Black Wind Ao Lie
Exit Corridor Directly
Yes
Take your position
Start
Everything is ready
Left three.
Second from the right
Far left
Third from the right
Right two.
Left four.
Third from the right
It was also advanced once.
Did I mishear Fifth Master's whistle
This time how is the right three
It should be
Third from the right
Turn it around, turn it around
The roller shutter building is lying to you
Don't turn.
Don't dawdle
Turn it around, turn it around
What are you doing?
You turned four times wrong
Fifth Master said it was right three
Fifth Brother
Are you okay?
I’m fine.
Wait for me a moment.
Be back soon.
Tianpeng Zhenyuan
Seventh Sister
You’re not hurt, are you?
Aren’t you hurt?
I’m fine.
It's a pity to let the shadow run away
I’m glad you’re okay.
How are you?
Tianpeng
Tianpeng, wake up, Tianpeng
Zhenyuan
Zhenyuan, wake up
My head really hurts.
Are you okay?
Zhenyuan
Fifth Master
People are fine
As long as the person is okay.
Fifth Master
The Buddha Master
Then I will follow
The order of dates on Jun Tanaka's diary
Read to you
April 15th
Our team
A line of 54 people
Led by Colonel Hatoyama himself
Enter the building
Instructions from Colonel Hatoyama
We're looking for the depths of the building.
There's a very secret thing
It can change the future
But what specifically
Hatoyama's reluctance to mention
May 3
Half a month's time
We're all lost in the maze of corridors
It was during this period
Zhang Qishan Enters Jiumen
Purge Changsha Secret Service
We should be in Changsha all inside
All nine were cleaned.
May 20
We were lost in the maze of corridors for a long time
Our physical strength has reached the limit
This building is too weird.
I didn’t expect it
Another thing happened at this time.
Something more bizarre.
There's a squad of eight missing
They seem to be right in front of us
But no matter how we chase
Always can't catch up
We tried a lot of ways
Finalization
They seem to have been
Keep a distance of 800 meters with US
Distance, right?
Maybe we need to do the opposite
We finally found out
The reason why I can't catch up with them
Seems to be because
Of that group of soldiers
Mix in something that doesn't belong to people
The Buddha Master
This is torn off again.
So many diaries.
Why have they all been torn off?
Continue
October 27
We 've been underground too long
I want to see the sun
We're about to join Colonel Hatoyama.
Complete the core mission of this top-secret report
But
We have no food
The Colonel has us stationed here
Cannot leave
But he often goes out alone.
Also don't know where to go
Hunger gradually swallowed our will
Someone even started to fall
Never wake up again
Just when I almost gave up hope
Colonel Hatoyama gave me a map
Let me go to a place
Someone up there is sending supplies down regularly.
Sometimes there are letters inside.
Looks like it's Colonel Hatoyama.
To find a way to connect to the outside
Provide us with supplies
Great!
But how on earth did he do it
8 November
Colonel Hatoyama said he would continue to walk in.
He already knows
What happened to this space?
The Colonel has us stationed here
He went deep with another group of people.
This back
It's The Daily Life record of Japanese soldiers here.
Until the very end
Jun Tanaka
Received a telegram
Last orders from Colonel Hatoyama
Gentlemen
The mission has entered the final stage
For the Great Empire of Japan
And the glory of His Majesty
Please cut your belly immediately to show your loyalty.
The righteousness will eventually be achieved.
And we
Will meet again
Record by Note
This is the wellhead where they go down
What the hell is down there?
The Buddha Master
Didn't Hatoyama say this
He already knows here
What the hell happened
Why send a telegram?
Let the above people collectively cut their bellies
If all the people who met him were dead
Does that mean
The people who went down with him
They all cut themselves to the belly
A Telegram for everyone to take their own life.
It's normal for them
This approach can guarantee
The secret never gets out
It's no good for us to guess again.
All the mysteries
It can only be solved by finding Hatoyama.
Buddha, your tone is a little hesitant.
Ember
This
Who is sending a telegram?
Is it forty-one
That’s impossible.
The radio frequency is different.
40-1 is even a telegram
Will also be sent to US
How can it be sent to the Japanese?
So
So it's the Japanese underground
Send us a telegram.
They're not dead yet
The Buddha Master
Translation finished
The situation is extremely dangerous
Emergency Request for Rescue
Buddha, they're asking for help.
Fifth Master
You truly are a genius.
I want to knock one for you now
What the hell is this place?
How to dazzle
Why is it here?
Yes, Fifth Master.
What on earth happened?
Fifth Master, you talk
It's okay.
You're just fascinated by the shadows.
He brought you here
Trapped you
Are you all right?
It's okay.
Fifth Master
The shadow did this to us.
Can't just let him run away
We have to catch him before Zhang Qishan
Yes, Fifth Master.
We can’t let him get away.
We must catch him
Since it's all right
Then listen up
One
Zhang Qishan, we can't control
We can't fold here for him
We gotta get out alive
Two
In fact, you almost died
I followed the building's guidelines
And cured you all
Fifth Master, you
You can't treat us like fools.
Do you believe me or not?
I
Fifth Master
Believe it or not
Letter letter
We believe in the letter of the fifth Master
Roller blind
Fifth Master
Pack your things
Getting ready to leave.
Yes
Tianpeng
Take a break.
Sit down
Seventh Sister
It’s time to leave.
What’s wrong?
If you believe you are right
Then just believe in yourself.
I will believe you too.
Good
Don't worry
Let's go.
Departure
Yes